(Mike:)You remember
the Thanksgiving game
(Mike:)when it snowed in Dallas?
Nineteen-ninety three. Leon Lett blew
the game in the final seconds
(Sheldon:)and the Dolphins
emerged victorious.
(Sheldon:)Then I finally got to do
my calculus.
(Mike:)I was so pissed,
I wanted to shoot my TV.
(Sheldon:)So was my dad.
And than he did.
(Howard:)-Anyone need a beer?
-Yeah.
(Howard:)Thank God.
(Mike:)So, does your dad
still live in Texas?
(Leonard:)No.
He died when I was 14.
(Mike:)I'm sorry to hear that.
(Sheldon:)So was the man who owned
the local liquor store.
(Sheldon:)He cried and cried.
(Howard:)-Here you go.
-Thanks.
(Mike:)So, if your dad died
when you were 14,
(Mike:)you were never old enough
to have a beer with the man.
(Sheldon:)No, sir.
(Sheldon:)He did try to give me one
for my high school graduation,
(Sheldon:)but I was 11 and my mom said, no.